# John M Berry

102 Cedar St Glasgow, KY 42141 270-834-9080 | johnb@bluegrassitc.com www.linkedin.com/in/john-berry-175b4914 Portfolio: https://john-m-berry.github.io/

## **Summary**

Very technical IT Support Technician has terrific troubleshooting and good interpersonal skills to assist customers with computer issues. Possesses a thorough knowledge of computer and network hardware, operating systems and software applications. 24 years of experience working as an IT Support Technician. Additionally, currently a student at BC Skills looking to further my career with this class of Web Development.

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

### Ultratech Computer Systems / Bluegrass IT & Computer Services, Glasgow, KY

Oct 1997 - Present

- Ability to configure Windows desktop computers under common scenarios.
- Adhering to wiring standards and using test tools.
- Configuring hardware, applications and network connectivity.
- Entry-level server management, configuration and support including coverage of Active Directory and Network Infrastructure, as well as Maintain, Troubleshoot, Install, Operate and Configure Basic Network hardware.
- Experience supporting Windows Operating Systems and application installation and support.
- PC Repair and Support including Virus removal.
- Possess good soft skills to work with clients in a user-friendly, non-technical language.
- Strong general troubleshooting methods and abilities.
- Peripheral installation, maintenance and troubleshooting.
- Excellent internet search skills to find answers when troubleshooting issues not seen before.

### Dunlap Sales, Glasgow, KY

June 1977 - September 1997

Asst Manager

- Troubleshooting and repair of Industrial Electronic Control Systems.
- Created and maintained computerized inventory control database.
- Maintained Office Computers and Networking.

#### **EDUCATION**

#### Junior Scholars Program, WKU

Summer 1973 6-hrs college credit summer between Jr & Sr Year of High School

WKU, Bowling Green

August 1974 – Dec 1976

Computer Science – Programming languages: BASIC, IBM Assembly Language, FORTRAN

**BC Skills Development Academy**, Glasgow/Bowling Green Currently enrolled in Web Development Cohort Program HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, SASS, JavaScript

January 2021 – Present

## **REFERENCES**

Barry Coffey - Owner, Glasgow Filter Products (270) 678-5765 g.info@glasgowfilter.com

Barry Harlow - Mgr., Dunlap Sales Electronic Repair (270) 651-5626

Jon Walbert - President, Walbert Trucking (270) 651-6784

Bernard Williams - Owner, Oliver Williams & Co. (270) 678-6980 bernardw@scrtc.com